[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "The longer this goes on do you get a bigger sense of foreboding about what may have happened to Hannah?", "question_tokens": ["The", "longer", "this", "goes", "on", "do", "you", "get", "a", "bigger", "sense", "of", "foreboding", "about", "what", "may", "have", "happened", "to", "Hannah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I absolutely do, especially if she's terrified having seen quite possibly what happened to her mother and possibly her kid brother, and she's in the clutches of this man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "do", ",", "especially", "if", "she", "'s", "terrified", "having", "seen", "quite", "possibly", "what", "happened", "to", "her", "mother", "and", "possibly", "her", "kid", "brother", ",", "and", "she", "'s", "in", "the", "clutches", "of", "this", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Will they build any kind of new property there?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "they", "build", "any", "kind", "of", "new", "property", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, they're talking about possibly a garden.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "talking", "about", "possibly", "a", "garden", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What is your reaction, first of all, to the scenes in Cleveland?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "to", "the", "scenes", "in", "Cleveland", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "You know, I just think it's a wonderful way of putting this all behind and starting to move forward.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "just", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "wonderful", "way", "of", "putting", "this", "all", "behind", "and", "starting", "to", "move", "forward", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cleveland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "And given the awful experience that you had to endure as a father, and it ended obviously happily for you but ends disastrously for so many, given that it ended well and it has done for these three victims in Cleveland, what is the best advice you would give them and indeed their families around them for how they can make a proper recovery?", "question_tokens": ["And", "given", "the", "awful", "experience", "that", "you", "had", "to", "endure", "as", "a", "father", ",", "and", "it", "ended", "obviously", "happily", "for", "you", "but", "ends", "disastrously", "for", "so", "many", ",", "given", "that", "it", "ended", "well", "and", "it", "has", "done", "for", "these", "three", "victims", "in", "Cleveland", ",", "what", "is", "the", "best", "advice", "you", "would", "give", "them", "and", "indeed", "their", "families", "around", "them", "for", "how", "they", "can", "make", "a", "proper", "recovery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, you know, I think everyone's journey through that recovery is different.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "everyone", "'s", "journey", "through", "that", "recovery", "is", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cleveland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "But what can you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "can", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "You know, my -- my advice is to stay positive and to, you know, just keep the pressure on.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "my", "--", "my", "advice", "is", "to", "stay", "positive", "and", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "just", "keep", "the", "pressure", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Is that your understanding of what happened here?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "understanding", "of", "what", "happened", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "From the sounds of it, it comes across as a tragic recipe of disaster.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "the", "sounds", "of", "it", ",", "it", "comes", "across", "as", "a", "tragic", "recipe", "of", "disaster", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "I mean, is it the kind of thing that that kind of African rock python would do if it got out of the cage and found itself near two young boys like that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "it", "the", "kind", "of", "thing", "that", "that", "kind", "of", "African", "rock", "python", "would", "do", "if", "it", "got", "out", "of", "the", "cage", "and", "found", "itself", "near", "two", "young", "boys", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, in the wild scenario, the ecosystem where this creature lives, they are known as being an aggressive species of snake.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "the", "wild", "scenario", ",", "the", "ecosystem", "where", "this", "creature", "lives", ",", "they", "are", "known", "as", "being", "an", "aggressive", "species", "of", "snake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Should anybody have these kind of things in a home environment (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "anybody", "have", "these", "kind", "of", "things", "in", "a", "home", "environment", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "I think it's only in specialized situations should private citizens have large snakes like this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "only", "in", "specialized", "situations", "should", "private", "citizens", "have", "large", "snakes", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Are we now seeing some of the more deadly effects of global warming on the wildlife in the arctic?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "now", "seeing", "some", "of", "the", "more", "deadly", "effects", "of", "global", "warming", "on", "the", "wildlife", "in", "the", "arctic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "ORWIN: It is -- Piers, it's very quite possible.", "answer_tokens": ["ORWIN", ":", "It", "is", "--", "Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "quite", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "You changed your mind?", "question_tokens": ["You", "changed", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I -- I have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "So when -- when New York Mayor Bloomberg was reported to say medical marijuana is the greatest hoax of all time, what do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "--", "when", "New", "York", "Mayor", "Bloomberg", "was", "reported", "to", "say", "medical", "marijuana", "is", "the", "greatest", "hoax", "of", "all", "time", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I'm surprised.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "surprised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New York Mayor Bloomberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "How quickly do you expect this to work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "quickly", "do", "you", "expect", "this", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Within like the first five minutes.", "answer_tokens": ["Within", "like", "the", "first", "five", "minutes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Sanjay?", "question_tokens": ["Sanjay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Well, I mean, look, the -- it can be difficult to -- to sort of stratify the legitimate patients who have use for cannabis, not only as a medication but as the only medication for their sufferings.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "look", ",", "the", "--", "it", "can", "be", "difficult", "to", "--", "to", "sort", "of", "stratify", "the", "legitimate", "patients", "who", "have", "use", "for", "cannabis", ",", "not", "only", "as", "a", "medication", "but", "as", "the", "only", "medication", "for", "their", "sufferings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Why (ph) -- isn't there an inconsistency in government policy?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "(", "ph", ")", "--", "is", "n't", "there", "an", "inconsistency", "in", "government", "policy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "``", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I -- I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Have you tried it?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "tried", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I have -- I have tried it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "--", "I", "have", "tried", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Well, what effect did it have on you compared to, say, drinking alcohol or whatever?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "effect", "did", "it", "have", "on", "you", "compared", "to", ",", "say", ",", "drinking", "alcohol", "or", "whatever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", ",", "VB", ",", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Well, you know, the irony isn't in some ways because I work on this documentary.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "irony", "is", "n't", "in", "some", "ways", "because", "I", "work", "on", "this", "documentary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Why do we want to support that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "we", "want", "to", "support", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Tough guy now?", "question_tokens": ["Tough", "guy", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Yes, yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Is that British humor?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "British", "humor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "It is my British humor.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "my", "British", "humor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Should he still be campaigning against this woman that you've supported today?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "he", "still", "be", "campaigning", "against", "this", "woman", "that", "you", "'ve", "supported", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "You know, I think whether or not he is, isn't really the question.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "whether", "or", "not", "he", "is", ",", "is", "n't", "really", "the", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"], "LOCATION": ["New Yorkers"]}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Or is he talking a lot about bunk (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "he", "talking", "a", "lot", "about", "bunk", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "You know, Anthony Weiner is asking New Yorkers for a second chance.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Anthony", "Weiner", "is", "asking", "New", "Yorkers", "for", "a", "second", "chance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Third chance?", "question_tokens": ["Third", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "But look, this is a serious job.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "look", ",", "this", "is", "a", "serious", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Is he trivializing just by staying in the race, given all that's been going on?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "trivializing", "just", "by", "staying", "in", "the", "race", ",", "given", "all", "that", "'s", "been", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Well, I think what this reminds us of is that when you take on a position like mayor of New York, you're a role model in one respect or another.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "what", "this", "reminds", "us", "of", "is", "that", "when", "you", "take", "on", "a", "position", "like", "mayor", "of", "New", "York", ",", "you", "'re", "a", "role", "model", "in", "one", "respect", "or", "another", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Your chances have got significantly better with Anthony Weiner's latest mishap, haven't (ph) they (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "chances", "have", "got", "significantly", "better", "with", "Anthony", "Weiner", "'s", "latest", "mishap", ",", "have", "n't", "(", "ph", ")", "they", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", ":", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "You know, I -- I felt good about my chances from day one.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "I", "felt", "good", "about", "my", "chances", "from", "day", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Do you think, as I do, that he's one of the great cheats in sporting history and should be kicked out of baseball?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", ",", "as", "I", "do", ",", "that", "he", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "great", "cheats", "in", "sporting", "history", "and", "should", "be", "kicked", "out", "of", "baseball", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Disgraceful.", "answer_tokens": ["Disgraceful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]